# ANDREA **MAZZEO**

# SOFTWARE ENGINEER



Pollate, Milan, Italy

28 September 1995

andrea.mazzeo95@gmail.com

+39 3498664241

https://andreamazzeo289.github.io

in www.linkedin.com/in/andreamazzeo289

# HARD SKILLS

#### SOFTWARE DEVELOPMENT

C, C++, QT, PYTHON, GIT, JIRA

## **COMPUTER VISION**

OPENCV, DEEP LEARNING, PYTORCH, KERAS, TENSORFLOW

## **EMBEDDED SYSTEMS**

FPGA, VHDL, VERILOG

## **WEB DEVELOPMENT**

JAVASCRIPT, HTML, CSS

# SOFT SKILLS

TEAM WORK
PROBLEM SOLVING
COMMUNICATION
AUTONOMY
TIME MANAGEMENT
ADAPTABILITY
LEADERSHIP

# LANGUAGES

ITALIAN • • • • •

ENGLISH • • • • •

# **PROFILE**

Versatile software engineer highly involved in research activities concerning computer vision and deep learning world. Always been passionate about low-level programming, where attention to detail is key. I'm willing to learn and improve with new challenging experiences.

# EXPERIENCE

**SOFTWARE ENGINEER** | SMART ROBOTS | 2021 - PRESENT

MAIN ACTIVITIES:

C++, CMake, QT, OpenCV, Computer Vision

TEACHING ASSISTANT | POLITECNICO DI MILANO | 2020 - 2021

COURSE:

Fundamentals of Computer Science

RESEARCH GRANT | POLITECNICO DI MILANO | 2020 - 2021

**RESEARCH TITLE:** 

Design and analysis of image processing applications for critical systems

# **EDUCATION**

## MASTER'S DEGREE IN COMPUTER SCIENCE AND ENGINEERING | 2017 - 2019

POLITECNICO DI MILANO

110 with honors / 110

THESIS

A Hybrid Fault Injection Framework for Image Processing Applications in FPGA

AREAS OF INTEREST:

Image processing and computer vision, embedded systems, firmware development, reconfigurable devices, computer architectures

# BACHELOR'S DEGREE IN COMPUTER SCIENCE AND ENGINEERING | 2014 - 2017

POLITECNICO DI MILANO

105 / 110

FINAL PROJECT:

Lorenzo il Magnifico – A multiplayer board games developed in Java

AREAS OF INTEREST:

Software engineering, full stack development, networking, database design

## HIGH SCHOOL DIPLOMA IN ELECTRONICS AND IT ENGINEERING | 2009 - 2014

ITCS ERASMO DA ROTTERDAM, BOLLATE

98 / 100

FINAL PROJECT:

A tracking system of an object using a CCD sensor

AREAS OF INTEREST:

FPGA, microcontroller ARM, robotics, PCB design

### PUBBLICATIONS

## USABILITY-BASED CROSS-LAYER RELIABILITY EVALUATION OF IMAGE PROCESSING APPLICATIONS

IEEE INTERNATIONAL SYMPOSIUM ON DEFECT AND FAULT TOLERANCE IN VLSI SYSTEMS 2021
C. Bolchini, L. Cassano, A. Mazzeo, A. Miele

#### APPROXIMATION-BASED FAULT-TOLERANCE IN IMAGE PROCESSING APPLICATIONS

IEEE TRANSACTIONS ON EMERGING TOPICS IN COMPUTING 2021

M. Biasielli, C. Bolchini, L. Cassano, A. Mazzeo, A. Miele

## ERROR MODELLING FOR IMAGE PROCESSING FILTERS ACCELERATED ONTO SRAM-BASED FPGAS

IEEE INTERNATIONAL SYMPSOSIUM ON ON-LINE TESTING AND ROBUST SYSTEM DESIGN | 2020

In compliance with the GDPR and the Italian Legislative Decree no. 196 dated 30/06/2003, I hereby authorize you to use and process my personal details contained in this document

C. Bolchini, L. Cassano, A. Mazzeo, A. Miele